mypromocenter.com 2016-02-07

# Dyna Optic

Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy of Dyna Optic

Dyna Optic has been practicing 100% permission based marketing since its inception. We have created this privacy policy to fully and transparently communicate our information gathering and dispersion practices. You are agreeing to our privacy policy in full when you

1\. click, open or preview any of the advertisement portion of our emails we send on for third party companies

2\. Give DynaOptic any personal private data through an online registration form, website or any other form of online media.

## Subscription Management

Dyna Optic believes in giving its subscribers notice and alternatives. If a subscriber chooses for any reason at any time to be removed from our database through our unsubscribe method that subscriber will no longer receive any emails from Dyna Optic. We will advise you, however, that you may still receive emails from affiliated websites or third party marketing companies you may be subscribed to. To unsubscribe from affiliate's emails visit the website of the affiliate to unsubscribe or follow the unsubscribe URL in the affiliate's email.

## Children's Privacy

Dyna Optic will never knowingly collect or attempt to collect information from children in 100% compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We use our secure consent-based marketing infrastructure to make sure all your data is protected. The infrastructure protects your data from unwanted access or modification. This infrastructure includes: physical security and technological security measures, encryption of fixed data, and internal and external firewalls.

## Information Gathering Process

The right to use the information we collect from our subscribers to help our clientele reach better audiences as well as help our own marketing data services is reserves. Personally identifiable information may be shared with affiliates that can include third party marketing companies, data aggregation companies, advertising agencies and/or affiliates. This information may be utilized to share information with consumers about products and services they may have an interest in, always keeping true to the guidelines stated in this specific privacy policy.

## Security Measures and CA Residents

Dyna Optic takes the security of our clients' information very seriously. Dyna Optic is 100% dedicated to protecting the safety of our subscribers online information. We uphold this commitment to safety by keeping log files for any websites that we own and/or operate. The log files we maintain may contain any of the following:

  * IP addresses
  * platform type
  * ISP
  * date/time stamp
  * browser type
  * referring/exit pages
  * amount of clicks to study behaviors, manage the site, shadow users' motion in the aggregate, and collect overall demographic intelligence for aggregate use.

## Possible Privacy Policy Updates

Dyna Optic suggests our users periodically revisit our privacy policy so they can remain educated of any possible revisions. It is possible a revision to our privacy policy may entitle us to utilize your personal data in a manner different from outlined in the privacy policy you originally agreed to at the time Dyna Optic collected your information. Dyna Optic is committed to posting any updates to our privacy policy to our site in a timely fashion. Any questions, comments, or concerns may be directed to Dyna Optic at admin@dynaoptic.com
